hi in today's installment of spring tips
您好在今天的 spring 技巧 中
we're going to look at basics for spring
我们要看一下春季的基础知识
just absolute basics of spring 101 if
只是春天101的绝对基础
you will we're gonna build an absolute
你会我们将建立一个绝对的
basic simple spring application using
基本的简单Spring应用程序使用
spring boot and before we can do that we
spring boot ，然后我们可以做到这一点，我们
kind of we need to have a sample
我们需要一个样本
application with which to work I'm going
我要使用的应用程序
to do so we're gonna create that
为此，我们将创建一个
application here in the spring tool
在spring tool中的应用
suite for the spring tool suite for is
spring tool suite 是
of course just a number of different
当然只是一些不同
plugins that work on top of either
可以在任何一个之上使用的插件
existing distributions or as a separate
现有发行版或单独发行
thing that you can download with its own
可以自己下载的东西
and you know eclipse distribution it's
而且你知道 eclipse 发行版
all open source so you can download a
全部开源，因此您可以下载
complete spring tool suite for
完整的 spring tool suite ，用于
distribution with the clips and
与 eclipse 一起分发
everything else all in one bundle that's
所有其他一切都捆绑在一起
what I would recommend that's just super
我建议的就是超级好
simple you just download the binary for
很简单，您只需下载二进制文件即可
your irrelevant operating system the
您不相关的操作系统
next Mac or or Windows and you're off to
下一台Mac或Windows，您将
the races
比赛
right so then you build a new
对，那么您就可以建立一个新的
application I'm gonna build an
我要建立一个应用程序
application here by going to file a new
通过在此处提交新申请
spring starter project it's gonna give
spring starter 项目
me a wizard and this wizard is just a an
我是一个向导，这个向导只是一个
easy way to configure your new
配置新的简单方法
application I'm going to build an upland
应用程序，我要建立一个高地
unification called reservation service
统一称为预订服务
I'll hit next it's gonna give me a bunch
我接下来要打，它会给我一堆
of different checkboxes or things that I
我不同的复选框或事物
could add to my application if I click
可以单击添加到我的应用程序中
on any of these different dropdowns for
在这些不同的下拉菜单中
our purposes I'm pretty happy I've
我们的目标我很高兴
already got reactor reactive web support
已经获得 reactor reactive web 支持
dev tools actuator reactive MongoDB
开发人员工具执行器反应式MongoDB
those are my frequently used ones for
这些是我经常使用的
for example so I I hit next and that
例如，所以我打了下一个
will give me a URL now keep in mind this
现在将给我一个URL请记住这一点
IDE is just a fancy front-end for the
IDE只是花哨的前端
start that's fingernail spring
开始那是指甲的春天
initializer and if you want to you could
初始值设定项，如果您愿意
in theory go to that initializer paste
理论上去那个初始化粘贴
this URL into a browser or console and
将该网址导入浏览器或控制台，
it would be you be given a zip file
它会给你一个压缩文件
download a zip file and they can unzip
下载一个zip文件，他们可以解压缩
it and then import the resulting maven
然后导入生成的Maven
project into IDE but why why bother with
项目到IDE，但为什么要打扰
all that extra work when you can just go
只要去就可以完成所有这些额外的工作
to the ID and choose file new starter
到ID并选择文件新启动器
and just hit go so that's what I've done
然后就去吧，这就是我所做的
here I've hit finished and then I give
在这里我打完了，然后我给
me a new project and then I'm gonna open
给我一个新项目，然后我要打开
up that project in my in my IDE I've got
在我的IDE中启动该项目
it here and I'm gonna choose file new
它在这里，我要选择新文件
you know I've already chosen all that
你知道我已经选择了所有
I've got a new application it's a spring
我有一个新的应用程序，这是春天
application okay in the spring
春季申请还可以
application
应用
old
旧
they spring at the end of the day at the
他们在一天结束时在
end of the day it's just a big bag of
一天结束的时候，
objects it's just a big bag of objects
只是一大袋东西
that you describe that you contribute
你描述自己的贡献
that you provide you define these
您提供的定义这些
objects represent your business logic
对象代表您的业务逻辑
and the goal is for spring to do as much
而目标是让春季做更多的事情
as possible for you without in in bang
在没有爆炸的情况下尽可能为您服务
upon your code about in you know in
根据您在中的代码
disturbing your business logic and so we
干扰您的业务逻辑，所以我们
we have this thing called dependency
我们有一个叫做依赖的东西
injection the idea behind dependency
注入依赖背后的想法
injection is very simple
注射很简单
let's suppose I wanted to build a um a a
假设我想建立一个um aa
API an HTTP API that supported access to
API支持访问的HTTP API
your data which is it Searle which is
您的数据是塞尔数据是
itself stored in a database which is a
本身存储在数据库中
which you facilitate access to through a
您可以方便地通过
repository ok these are different
好的，这些不同
logical layers and application you've
您拥有的逻辑层和应用程序
got the web tier you've got the
获得了网络层
repository web which represents that the
代表网站的
data access object it's just another
数据访问对象
object and then the repository in turn
对象，然后依次转到存储库
depends upon and manages a reference to
依赖并管理对
your database the actual connection to
您的数据库的实际连接
your database right you've got three
您的数据库对，您有三个
different objects the rest api depending
rest api 取决于不同的对象
on the repository depending on the
在存储库上，具体取决于
database if you tell spring about these
数据库，如果你告诉春天这些
objects then you can centralize the
对象，然后您可以集中
definition of these objects you can keep
您可以保留这些对象的定义
them in one place and if you want to
他们在一个地方，如果你想
change them you just change them in that
改变他们，你只是改变他们
one place and then all the code in the
一个地方，然后所有的代码
end the application that depends on
结束依赖的应用程序
those objects can be updated accordingly
这些对象可以相应地更新
similarly you don't have to do all the
同样，您不必做所有的事情
work right so some let's say you want to
工作正常，所以有人说你想
build an it should be service well
建立一个应该很好的服务
what's involved in building an HTTP
建立HTTP涉及什么
service well you need a web server so
服务很好，您需要Web服务器，因此
there's a good few days of work just you
只是你有好几天的工作
know learning all about web servers and
知道学习有关Web服务器的所有知识，以及
standing it up and configuring a routing
站起来并配置路由
and then connecting that routing to your
然后将该路由连接到您的
object somewhere in your JVM code and
在JVM代码中的某个对象
then once you've done that now what well
然后一旦完成，现在怎么样
you now you need to get a pointer to
您现在需要获取一个指向
that repository and that in turn needs
该存储库，进而需要
to manage a reference to the database
管理对数据库的引用
who creates the database you could
谁可以创建数据库
certainly do that right but why not
当然可以，但是为什么不呢？
let's spring do that for you let's bring
让我们春天为您做，让我们带来
boot in part in particular do that for
引导部分特别是为了
you
您
so there's two things going on here one
所以这里有两件事
is you can define objects and then teach
你可以定义对象然后教
them how to wire themselves together
他们如何将自己联系在一起
using spring and if you want more more
使用spring，如果您想要更多
help before want for example the web
需要帮助之前，例如网络
server to be provided if you want for
要提供的服务器
example the database to automatically be
示例数据库自动
created it's what these kinds of things
创造了这些东西
then you can go to spring boot okay but
那你可以去 spring boot 了，但是
the but it all starts with spring and
但这一切都从春天开始
all starts with the understanding how
一切都始于对如何
things relate to each other so let's say
事情彼此相关，所以说
I want to build a a simple REST API okay
我想建立一个简单的REST API
so let's say I have an application that
所以说我有一个应用程序
manages access to data through MongoDB
通过MongoDB管理对数据的访问
okay so I'm gonna say class reservation
好吧，我要说 class 预约
rest controller and this is gonna be an
rest controller ，这将是一个
object that's going to manage access to
将用于管理访问权限的对象
my data in MongoDB so I say private
我在MongoDB中的数据，所以我说私有
final and what I need I guess I guess I
最后的和我需要的我猜我猜我
could start off with a very low level
可能从一个很低的水平开始
I need a service of some sort of a
我需要某种服务
repository there at least I could say
至少我可以说那里的资料库
class reservation repository and then
类保留存储库，然后
this would I guess at some point need
我想在某个时候需要
access to a Mongo database wouldn't it
访问Mongo数据库不是吗
it's a Mongo database there we are
这是一个Mongo数据库
DB and I'm gonna in I'm gonna say alt
DB，我要说alt
command s and that LS has an Sam
命令，并且LS有一个Sam
and then I'll override generating
然后我将覆盖生成
constructor from my fields there we are
从我那里的构造函数
okay so I've created an object that has
好吧，所以我创建了一个具有
a dependency which I've expressed here
我在这里表达的依赖性
through the constructor on that Mongo
通过该Mongo上的构造函数
database we don't know where that comes
数据库，我们不知道那是哪里
from and my rest controller in turn
来自我的 rest controller
private you know private final
私人，你知道私人决赛
reservation repository like so
像这样的预订库
repository same trick I'm gonna do a alt
仓库相同的技巧，我要做一个替代
command s I'll generate the constructor
命令s我将生成构造函数
voila all right not bad so I've got that
瞧，还不错，所以我知道了
you know that's how do these things get
你知道这是怎么得到的
wired together well one way to do that
很好地连接在一起的一种方法
one way to get these things to wired
一种将这些东西连接起来的方法
together is to be very explicit you can
在一起是非常明确的，你可以
use Java configuration so I can say
使用Java配置，所以我可以说
class reservation configuration okay and
类预订配置还可以，
here it's just an object that spring
这只是春天的一个物体
knows about that because I've annotated
知道这一点，因为我已经注释了
it with a marker annotation so called
它带有一个标记注释，即所谓的
stereotyped annotation called add
构造型注释称为add
configuration at configuration
配置时配置
ultimately is annotate with a component
最终用组件注释
and we'll talk about
我们将谈论
component again but this is the
组件再次，但这是
annotation that tells spring to sweep up
注释告诉弹簧清扫
any class that's been annotated with it
任何带有注释的类
or by an or or annotated with an
或以或或以注释
annotation that is itself trans of lis
注释本身就是lis的反义词
annotated with it it'll sweep up that
加上注释，它将扫除
that object for managing right a little
该对象用于一点点管理
manage it for us so it's gonna see this
为我们管理它，它会看到这个
configuration annotation it's gonna see
将会看到的配置注释
that it's a component a component is
它是一个组件，一个组件是
enough for spring to manage it but that
足以让春天来管理它，但是那
configuration goes one step further it
配置更进一步
tell spring that there are methods in
告诉春天，里面有方法
this object this class that in turn
这个对象这个类
produce object instances for you
为您生产对象实例
we call those in the spring world we
我们称那些春季世界的人
call those resulting objects beans an
称这些结果对象为bean
object that's been managed by spring is
弹簧管理的对象是
a bean and so you create a method that's
一个豆子，所以您创建了一个
annotated with at being so let's say
注释着被这样说
reservation rest controller okay
预订 rest controller 还可以
reservation rest controller and there's
预订 rest controller ，还有
my controller right there very simple
我的控制器就很简单
right and I want that controller to
对的，我希望那个控制器
depend on my reservation repository it's
取决于我的预订库
a reservation repository reservation
预留存储库预留
repository and we say return new
仓库，我们说返回新
reservation repository okay and that
保留资料库还可以
depends on a data source well my
完全取决于数据源
goodness bean Mongo database right and
善良豆Mongo数据库权利和
for now I guess we can just return no I
现在我想我们只能返回不，我
I don't know how to create a Mongo
我不知道如何创建一个Mongo
database offhand but let's just return
暂存数据库，但让我们返回
null for now we know that that needs to
暂时为空，我们知道这需要
get sorted out eventually right but just
最终得到解决，但只是
not now okay so I'm gonna inject I'm
现在不行，所以我要注入
gonna tell spring to inject or to
要告诉春天注射或
satisfy the requirement for this this
满足此要求
collaborating object like so I'm gonna
像这样的协作对象
tell it to provide it in the the the
告诉它在提供
prototype for this method okay and
此方法的原型还可以
finally my rest controller here
最后我的 rest controller 在这里
similarly it needs a pointer to the
同样，它需要一个指向
server there were posters I'm gonna say
服务器上有我要说的海报
a new reservation rest controller I'll
一个新的预订 rest controller
provide a pointer to the repository like
提供指向存储库的指针，例如
so reservation repository are are
所以预订库是
Arar all right look at that so there's
Arar很好看，所以有
my three objects that are related to
与我有关的三个对象
each other one depends on the other the
彼此依赖
database we haven't you know that's a
数据库，我们不知道那是一个
big old to do right there we've got the
大老就在那里做，我们已经
rest controller but of course we don't
rest controller ，但我们当然不
have a web server yet so if you look at
有一个网络服务器，所以如果你看
this configuration this is nice you know
这种配置，这很好，你知道
but we don't really have a you know how
但是我们真的没有一个你知道如何
do we what does it mean for this press
我们对这家出版社意味着什么
controller to be an API that that gets
控制器成为要获取的API
exposed to the Internet I could have
暴露给我本可以拥有的互联网
annotations like this I could say at get
这样的注释我可以在获取时说
mapping forward slash reservations and
映射正斜杠保留和
have an endpoint here that returns you
在这里有一个端点可以返回您
know all the data so return this dot RR
知道所有数据，因此返回该点RR
dot repository and what do I want to
点存储库，我想做什么
support well I'm gonna support a method
好好支持我会支持一种方法
called find all I want to find all the
叫找到所有我想找到所有的
data reactively okay so we don't know
反应性好的数据，所以我们不知道
how this is gonna work but we know we
这将如何工作，但我们知道我们
want to support it okay so now a couple
想支持它，所以现在有几个
things to break down here first of all
首先要分解的事情
it flux is a kind of like a collection -
它的通量就像一个集合-
it's a type that will manage mediate
这是一种可以处理中介的类型
access to a stream of data that will be
访问将要
delivered to us asynchronously not right
异步交付给我们不对
now but perhaps later also I want two
现在，但也许以后我也要两个
men in Stinson's the type of reservation
斯廷森男人的保留类型
this is a whole service designed to
这是一项旨在
support managing entities of type
支持类型的管理实体
resignation so let's go ahead and define
辞职，让我们继续定义
that type okay let's go ahead and say
这个类型好吧，让我们继续说
create class reservation gonna be a you
创建课程预订将成为您
know brand new object it's gonna have
知道它会拥有的全新对象
what it's gonna have a field private
这将有一个私人领域
string ID this will be the ID that will
字符串ID，这将是
be stored in a MongoDB document and then
将其存储在MongoDB文档中，然后
private string reservation name so there
私人字符串保留名称，所以在那里
we go there's my my basic entity okay
我们去那是我的基本实体
this is obviously Java so I need some
这显然是Java，所以我需要一些
some Gators and some setters and so on
一些鳄鱼和二传手等等
so I'm going to say alt shift or sorry
所以我要说alt shift或对不起
command alt s and I'll generate some
命令alt，我会生成一些
getters and setters for my my fields
我所在领域的吸气器和吸气器
there select all very good generate all
那里选择所有很好产生所有
to command s for the constructors right
命令s的构造函数
I don't want that and the two string
我不想要那两个字符串
okay and I want the Constructors using
好的，我希望构造函数使用
those fields as well and then we want
这些领域，然后我们想要
one more constructor with no fields so
一个没有字段的构造函数，所以
do you select all generate and there we
您是否选择了所有生成，并且在那里
go there's my um my basic arrange of a
我的基本安排是
basic object okay that's all done for me
基本对象好了，这一切都为我完成
now and here I want to say find all
现在和这里我想说的是找到所有
right we don't know how to get that
是的，我们不知道该如何获得
result yet but we know that's what we
结果还没有，但是我们知道那就是我们
want to do okay
想做得好
so there we go there's my HTTP endpoint
所以我们去那里是我的HTTP端点
I'm telling I'm telling the spring hey I
我告诉我告诉春天嘿我
want you to take this method and invoke
希望您采用此方法并调用
it whenever somebody makes an HTTP GET
每当有人进行HTTP GET时它
request to force reservations on our web
要求在我们的网站上强行预订
server which we haven't defined it we
我们尚未定义的服务器
don't know what's gonna come from but we
不知道会发生什么，但是我们
know that we want it right and we've
知道我们想要它正确，我们已经
told Spring look I have a constructor
告诉Spring，我有一个构造函数
provide a pointer a reference to the
提供一个指向
reservation repository that's this thing
预订资料库就是这个东西
down here and the definitions that live
在这里和生活的定义
down here but the construction logic for
在这里，但施工逻辑
all these things lives in this
所有这些东西都生活在这个
configuration class well turns out
配置类好结果
that's a little a little bit of a
那有点
disconnect there in this case it makes
在这种情况下断开连接
sense obviously the Mongo database I
明显感觉到我的Mongo数据库
have to construct the instance because
必须构造实例，因为
there's no way to do otherwise but in
除此以外，别无选择
this case why not just have the
这种情况下为什么不只是
definition of the objects and their
对象及其定义
wiring live in the live on the component
在组件的带电状态下布线
class itself and live on the object code
类本身并依靠目标代码
itself so I'm gonna annotate this with
本身，所以我要用
another stereotype annotation or another
另一个构造型注释或另一个
marker annotation mm-hmm called a tress
标记注释mm-hmm称为发束
controller and it follows the same rules
控制器，它遵循相同的规则
as that configuration and that's that
作为该配置，就是这样
component because it's in this package
组件，因为它在此软件包中
is gonna be discovered by the components
会被组件发现
can when the application starts up
可以在应用程序启动时
similarly I've got a repository I could
同样，我有一个可以
say this is a repository like so and the
说这是一个像这样的仓库
repository is itself meta annotated with
存储库本身带有元注释
a component so I've got all these things
一个组件，所以我拥有了所有这些东西
you know they've got repository I've got
你知道他们有仓库我有
risk controller at configuration and
配置时的风险控制者
these are my different objects and
这些是我不同的对象，
spring is gonna look at these marker
春天要去看看这些标记
annotations it's going to sweep up these
注释将清除这些
objects and metals in forests and the
森林和森林中的物体和金属
dependencies one upon the other is
相互依存是
implied by the types and the
由类型和
Constructors and and so on so this is
构造函数等等，所以这是
very very you know I think a very clean
非常非常你知道我认为很干净
approach now the only thing here is this
现在唯一的方法是
database well you know I I do need to
数据库，您知道II确实需要
define that at some point I need to have
定义在某个时候我需要
that definition somewhere but we're
这个定义在某处，但我们
using spring boot
使用 spring boot
and so spring boot can help us the rest
所以 spring boot 可以帮助我们休息
of the way it can help us go from you
可以帮助我们脱离您的方式
know having these objects that have
知道拥有这些具有
these HTTP endpoints that which is
这些HTTP端点
already pretty convenient and we can
已经很方便了，我们可以
ignore Nano for example what it means to
例如忽略Nano
wire up our object to our web server now
现在将对象连接到Web服务器
we can thanks to spring boot we can
我们可以感谢 spring boot
ignore even more we can actually say for
我们甚至可以忽略更多
example to spring boot look you've got
spring boot 看起来的例子
this file palm that XML this is your
XML，这是您的这个文件
build file and in there you've got
建立文件，在那里
spring boot start up dead among would it
spring boot 启动死了吗
be reactive that means that by default
反应性的，这意味着默认情况下
spring boot is going to try and create a
春天的引导将尝试创建一个
connection to the localhost running
连接到正在运行的localhost
instance of MongoDB and so I can drop
MongoDB的实例，所以我可以删除
that bean it'll just provide a default
该bean，它将仅提供默认值
being for us and so all the code that
为我们而所有的代码
needs it will inject it mmm that means
需要它会注入它，这意味着
that I can actually run this code if I
如果我可以实际运行此代码
want to inject it but again looking at
想注入它，但再次看
this code this is actually you know
这段代码，实际上你知道
let's suppose I built this code let's
假设我建立了这段程式码
suppose I did that I I could do that but
假设我做到了II可以做到，但是
talking to the database like this is
与数据库交谈是这样的
very low-level so instead another thing
很低级，所以另一件事
that makes spring so useful that we had
这使春天变得如此有用，以至于我们有了
these abstractions these are very low
这些抽象这些非常低
level abstractions that make working
使工作正常的级别抽象
with tedious infrastructure things like
繁琐的基础设施之类的东西
databases and message queues and and so
数据库和消息队列等等
on easier to work with it boils down all
在更容易使用它归结为所有
the sort of boilerplate code it reduces
它减少的样板代码的种类
that down to the barest minimum essence
降至最低的最低限度
of the thing that you're trying to do so
您正在尝试这样做的事情
instead of using MongoDB base directly
而不是直接使用MongoDB base
instead of doing that directly I'm gonna
而不是直接这样做，我要
use a reactive Mongo template okay and
使用反应性Mongo模板好吧，
the reactive Mongo template is just a
反应性Mongo模板只是一个
convenience client that you can use to
您可以用来的便利客户
talk to I'm going to be and that will be
和我说话，那将会是
the thing that I introduced in the
我在介绍的东西
inject in my constructor like so once
像这样一次注入我的构造函数
I've done that I've got a reference to
我已经完成了对我的引用
that and I can use that to good effect I
我可以用它来取得良好的效果
can actually say now to Mungo
现在可以对芒戈说
look please go to the template go to the
看，请转到模板，转到
database for me and find all documents
我的数据库并找到所有文件
and match them match them or map them to
并匹配它们匹配它们或将它们映射到
my reservation class okay and so it's in
我的预订班还可以，所以在
order for it to do that it's gonna need
为了做到这一点，它将需要
some information on this reservation
有关此预订的一些信息
it's going to need to know how
它需要知道如何
map the ID this is the ID field right
映射ID这是ID字段右侧
the document ID and it'll need to know
文档ID，它需要知道
that this is a document like so all
这是一个像这样的文件
right so there's my document now once
对，所以现在有我的文件
I've done that I think that's pretty
我已经做到了，我认为那很漂亮
pretty straightforward don't you that
很简单，不是吗
that actually works but you know what
确实有效，但是你知道吗
this kind of work easy though it is it's
这种工作很简单，尽管它是
still a little low-level consider that I
还有一点低层次的考虑，我
still have to create a crud you know
仍然需要创建一个小结
could I have to support all the kind of
我能不能支持所有的
crud lifecycle methods I have to create
我必须创建的关键生命周期方法
read update delete I have to go to
阅读更新删除我必须去
support custom queries and all that kind
支持自定义查询等
of stuff
的东西
so we can go one step further spring
所以我们可以再往前走一步
boot has automatically Auto configured
启动已自动配置
for us spring data spring data is a
对我们来说spring data spring data是一个
umbrella project that provides the
总括项目
ability to based on an interface
基于接口的能力
definition automatically provide a
定义自动提供
definition of the object that satisfies
满足的对象的定义
that definition so reservation
该定义如此保留
repository extends reactive Mongo
存储库扩展了反应性Mongo
repository this is going to be a
仓库这将是一个
repository that manages access to a
用于管理对
entity or document in this case of type
在这种情况下的实体或文件
reservation so command one import that
保留，所以命令一个导入
right look at that not bad so it already
正确的看那还不错，所以它已经
has methods if you look at this reactive
有方法，如果你看这个反应
manga repository it already provides
它已经提供的漫画库
methods for inserting inserting based on
插入的方法基于
a collection inserting based on a
基于一个插入的集合
reactive publisher we can find all given
反应性发布者，我们可以找到所有给定的
a example that we can look at find all
一个例子，我们可以看看找到所有
based on more examples in a sorting
基于排序中的更多示例
condition
条件
it supports reactive sorting repository
它支持反应式分类库
which says find all given a sort
说找到所有给定的
condition
条件
reactive crud repository supports saving
反应堆存储库支持保存
saving all saving all finding my ID
保存所有保存所有找到我的ID
finding my ID give it a publisher test
找到我的身份证给发布者测试
checking if it exists and then finding
检查它是否存在，然后找到
all which is actually the thing that we
这实际上是我们所要做的
defined or started to define earlier so
定义或开始更早定义
all these different kinds of common
所有这些不同种类的共同点
lifecycle methods are implied in this
隐含生命周期方法
interface and that's all we need to do
界面，这就是我们需要做的
spring data will take this interface and
弹簧数据将采用此接口，
provide an object that we can then
提供一个我们可以
inject this is the right here right I'm
我在这里注入正确的权利
gonna I can inject this by type if I put
我可以按类型注入
a breakpoint here on line 31 at runtime
运行时在此处的第31行有一个断点
I'll see that I don't actually have this
我会发现我实际上没有这个
interface obviously you can't just
界面显然你不能只是
inject it there's no such thing as a
注入它没有像
runtime you know instance of interface
运行时，您知道接口实例
you have a type that implements an
你有一个实现
interface so I'll have a pointer to a
接口，所以我将有一个指向
reference to an object that
引用一个对象
implements reservation or plaster that's
实施保留或
in my spring petticoat so now I have a
在我的春季衬裙里，现在我有一个
very simple API that depends upon the
非常简单的API，具体取决于
repository there posit or ease down to
在那里存放或缓和到
just an interface I can create custom
只是我可以创建自定义界面
finder methods as well I can say I want
查找器方法以及我可以说我想要
to find all instances of this
找到这个的所有实例
reservation by the reservation name
通过预订名称进行预订
field so that like that and that's it
领域，这样，仅此而已
that's the that'll actually get
那是实际上会得到的
implemented that based on convention
根据惯例实施
spring dad is gonna say I'm gonna create
春爸爸要说我要创造
a beasts on query that looks at all the
在查询中的野兽
documents among the DB and finds the
数据库中的文档并找到
longing to be documents that have the
渴望成为具有
attribute reservation name whose value
属性保留名称，其值
is equal to the value that we provide
等于我们提供的价值
here in the RN parameter and that just
在RN参数中，
gets done for us we don't have to
为我们做好了，我们不必
implement that either it's just done for
实现只是为了完成
us automatically so that's all spring
我们自动，所以这是整个春天
boot now of course I have got this rest
现在启动，我当然已经休息了
controller spring boot it's
控制器弹簧启动
automatically gonna make sure that
自动确保
that's a that's um you know a working
那是个你知道工作的地方
rest controller this is one way to
rest controller ，这是一种方法
create a rest controller by the way
顺便创建一个 rest controller
there's two different ways in spring you
春天你有两种不同的方式
can actually use this style which is
可以实际使用这种样式
very nice or you can use the new
非常好，或者您可以使用新的
functional reactive style so let's try
功能反应式，让我们尝试
that router functions write a function
路由器功能写一个功能
server response routes return router
服务器响应路由返回路由器
functions dots route I'm going to
功能点路线我要去
provide a request predicate dot get
提供请求谓词点获取
forward slash reservations and this
正斜杠保留和这个
thing that is required over here is a
这里需要的是一个
object of type handler function so I
类型处理程序函数的对象，所以我
could provide a lambda there but what I
可以在那里提供一个lambda，但是我
like to do is to use Java 8 method
喜欢做的就是使用Java 8方法
references so I'm gonna say class
参考，所以我要说课
reservation handler okay and this is
预订处理程序好，这是
just gonna be a regular old spring bean
会成为普通的老春豆
knows nothing special about it just an
对此一无所知
object that I want to bring to manage
我要带来管理的对象
for me and I'm gonna say and and you
为了我，我要说和你
know I'm gonna say I went to a it's
知道我要说我去了
going to implement handler response or
要实现处理程序响应或
handler right
处理权
it's gonna implement the second type
它会实现第二种
that's required here for the route
这是路线所需的
method yeah there we go and the type
方法是的，我们去了，类型
that's required the thing that's
这需要的是
required is a handler function so I'm
需要的是处理程序功能，所以我
going to create a handler function I'm
要创建一个处理程序函数
gonna implement handler function of type
要实现类型的处理函数
of server response like so implements
这样的服务器响应
and their function of type of server
及其服务器类型的功能
response okay so there's my my custom
响应好，所以这是我的习惯
handler being import that import this
导入此处理程序
import that and we're going to have to
导入，我们将不得不
implement those methods so I'll say
实现那些方法，所以我会说
command 1 and you can see that the the
命令1，您可以看到
method is it's expecting is handle given
期望的方法是给定的句柄
a server request and actually I don't
服务器请求，实际上我没有
even need to implement this we can use a
甚至需要实现这一点，我们可以使用
method reference so I'll get rid of that
方法参考，所以我将摆脱它
and there we go there's my my handler
然后我们去那里是我的经理
and I'll say that this is the handler
我会说这是处理程序
that provides by ID
由ID提供
okay so reservations ID and this handler
好的，所以保留ID和此处理程序
in order to do its work will require a
为了完成其工作，需要
pointer to the reservation repository
指向保留库的指针
for reservation repository like so and
像这样的预订库
alt command S generate the constructor
alt命令S生成构造函数
and there you go
然后你去
so there you go there's my custom
所以你去那里是我的习惯
handler method I'm going to say that I
处理程序方法我要说的是
want to inject that collaborating object
想要注入合作对象
here all they provided collaborating
在这里，他们提供了合作
reference here to the handler and and I
这里参考处理程序和我
use a method reference in Java 8 and ER
在Java 8和ER中使用方法参考
by ID there we go there's my my custom
通过ID我们去那里是我的习惯
method and you know that's a very
方法，你知道这是一个非常
straightforward piece of code obviously
很简单的一段代码
we can abbreviate it a little bit let's
我们可以缩写一下
use command 1 again to a convert to a
再次使用命令1转换为
static import okay very nice use that
静态导入还可以，很好用
again static import very good so that's
再次静态导入非常好，所以
actually a separate way of providing the
实际上是提供
rest in point let's actually you know
休息一下让我们实际上你知道
implement that now to say server
现在实现说服务器
responds well first of all
首先反应良好
we're going to say request dot path
我们要说的是请求点路径
variable is equal to ID string ID equals
变量等于ID字符串ID等于
and what I want to do someone look up
和我想做的人抬头
the record by its ID so I'll say this
记录的ID，所以我会这样说
step repository
步骤库
dot find by ID passing in the ID and
通过ID输入ID和
this will give me a publisher of
这会给我一个出版商
reservation mono resume that's actually
保留单声道简历，实际上
a another publisher mono and flux are
另一个出版商mono和flux是
both publishers by ID results okay and
通过ID的两个发布者都可以，并且
now I'm gonna send a response back to
现在我要回覆
the client so it's a response that okay
客户，这是一个好的回应
that body is by ID results sitting in
该身体是通过ID结果坐在
reservation dot class alright there's
保留点类不错
our whole piece of code clean that up a
我们的整个代码清理了一个
little bit here there we go so that is
一点点，我们去了那里，那是
the the hold handler the rest controller
保留处理程序，其余控制器
the repository all of that is here very
所有的仓库都在这里
simple application let's go ahead and
简单的应用程序，让我们继续前进，
run this okay so let's go ahead and run
运行这个好吧，让我们继续运行
this application and you can see I've
这个应用程序，你可以看到我已经
got here the boot dashboard so the
到这里启动仪表板，所以
dashboard is running it's are in the
仪表板正在运行中
background it sits there on the local
它坐在当地的背景
thing I'm just go ahead and I'm gonna go
我只是去做，我要去
ahead and hit click I'm gonna go ahead
前进并点击“点击”，我将继续前进
and click run it'll start the
然后点击运行，它将启动
application and you know as the
应用程序，您知道
application spins up you can see that
应用程序旋转起来，您可以看到
it's on the you know everything's fine
在你知道一切都很好的情况下
on the console there we don't have any
在控制台上，我们没有任何
data I didn't actually write any data to
我实际上没有写任何数据的数据
the database here so maybe I should
这里的数据库，所以也许我应该
create some code to write some sample
创建一些代码以编写一些示例
data to the database so I'll create an
数据到数据库，所以我将创建一个
initializer it's going to implement the
初始化程序将实现
application run or a callback interface
应用程序运行或回调接口
they call back runner the application
他们回叫亚军申请
runner callback interface is a a spring
跑步者回调界面是春季
boot and at a type rather and I'm going
引导，并以一种类型，而我要
to import that add the unemployment
进口增加失业
method and then
方法然后
when the application starts up I'm gonna
当应用程序启动时，我要
inject the reservation repository here
在此处注入预订存储库
we'll see that like so repo and we're
我们将看到这样的回购，
going to just provide that into the
只是将其提供给
constructor and as before and you can
构造函数和以前一样，您可以
see on the bottom here as I'm making
在我做的时候在底部看到
changes my code spring is restarting yep
更改我的代码弹簧正在重新启动
just automatically trying to reload the
只是自动尝试重新加载
changed code of course sometimes it's
当然，更改代码有时是
failing so we're getting these you know
失败，所以我们得到这些你知道
unsightly errors there but that's okay
那里难看的错误，但是没关系
that's you know it's it's not compiled
那就是你知道那是没有编译的
code so sometimes it doesn't work when
代码，因此有时在某些情况下不起作用
it does compile it runs and it works
它确实可以编译运行并且可以正常工作
just fine so here I'm gonna write some
很好，所以我在这里写一些
date I'm gonna say flux just a B C and
约会，我要说的是公元前
I'm gonna map each name to a new
我要把每个名字都映射到一个新名字
reservation you know for the ID name and
您知道ID名称的预订，以及
then flatmap are I'm gonna save it to
然后将平面图保存到
this repo dot save our and then that
这个仓库点保存我们的，然后那个
results in an object that will actually
产生一个实际上会
save data today's actually you know
今天保存数据，实际上你知道
better yet I'll just do subscribe there
更好，但我会在那里订阅
subscribe okay so there's my there's my
订阅好，所以有我的有我的
whole thing that's just gonna write data
整个事情都会写数据
to the database you know what actually
到数据库中，您实际上知道什么
bet it I'll leave it as flatmap and I'll
打赌，我将其保留为平面图，然后
say dot subscribe our system okay
说点订阅我们的系统好
reservation to string there we go so
保留字符串在那里我们去
there's my application it started up
有我的应用程序启动了
immediately there's a results on the
马上有结果
console so that's working alright we can
控制台，这样就可以了，我们可以
see that our simple bit of code is
看到我们的简单代码是
working when I start the application up
启动应用程序时正常工作
an interesting thing happens so let's go
发生一件有趣的事情，让我们开始吧
ahead and close all the other tabs get
并关闭所有其他标签
that back as I started up some my
当我开始一些我的
application becomes green Ian in certain
应用程序在某些方面变成绿色的伊恩
places do you see the spring tool suite
你在哪里看到 spring tool suite
for focus is not on development time
专注于开发时间
validation because
验证，因为
really spring is just Java right you
真的春天只是Java对吧
don't need anything - there's nothing
不需要什么-什么都没有
more than the compiler and you know your
不仅仅是编译器，而且您知道您的
your your understanding of the API is to
您对API的理解是
really guide you here right they the the
真的在这里指导您
runtime the sort of resulting runtime
运行时产生的运行时
behavior of the application is
该应用程序的行为是
determined entirely by spring so there's
完全由春天决定，所以
no like static analysis that we can do
不像我们可以做的静态分析
that would be without reimplemented
那将没有重新实现
spring for the ID there's no point in
春天的ID没有意义
doing that either
要么这样做
so instead spring gives off information
所以春天发出了信息
about its running application and that
关于其正在运行的应用程序以及
information feeds back into the IDE so
信息反馈到IDE中，因此
you can see that here as this sort of
您可以在这里看到这种
little green highlights for different
不同的小绿色亮点
types and different things in the
类型和不同的事物
application you can see for example if
您可以查看应用程序，例如
you mouse over at component it shows me
您将鼠标悬停在组件上会向我显示
that this is a bean that is that it's
这是一个豆子，就是
called initializer the ID of the bean is
称为初始化器的bean的ID是
called initializer it's running in this
称为初始化程序，它在此运行
process and this inside this is a scope
过程，这是一个范围
let's find this inside this class-based
让我们在这个基于类的内部找到它
in this configuration class we can see
在此配置类中，我们可以看到
it's a bean that lives inside of the
这是生活在里面的豆子
reservation repository type you know
您知道的预订存储库类型
that we I'm sorry we can see that this
很抱歉，我们可以看到
dependency up here with the arrow is
依赖关系在这里用箭头是
injected into the initializer the bean
将bean注入初始化程序
itself is called a reservation
本身称为保留
reservation repository but it lives in
预订存储库，但它位于
this type this is an interesting thing
这种类型，这很有趣
here this these arrows are very
在这里，这些箭头非常
interesting in swing tools before it's
在秋千工具中很有趣
giving us the dependency graph it says
给我们它说的依赖图
here my route thing my route to bean
这是我的路线，我通往豆的路线
depends on the handler and that's what
取决于处理程序，这就是
the left arrow means that means that the
左箭头表示这意味着
thing on which this watermark sits
水印所在的东西
depends on the thing in the watermark
取决于水印中的东西
the initializer depends on the
初始化程序取决于
reservation reservation repository going
预约预约仓库去
the other other way we can see oh and
另一种方式，我们可以看到哦，
there's another example by the way my
还有另一个例子
router function and my reservation
路由器功能和我的预订
repository both depend on sorry my
仓库都取决于对不起我
reservation handler depends on the
保留处理程序取决于
reservation repository but my router
保留资料库，但我的路由器
function depends on the reservation
功能取决于预约
handler so this is the things that
处理程序，所以这就是
depend on this object and this is the
取决于这个对象，这是
thing that is injected into this object
注入这个物体的东西
because it depends on them okay so both
因为这取决于他们好，所以两者
directions right me
方向对我
it depends on my reservation handler
这取决于我的预订处理程序
that means our reservation handler
这意味着我们的预订处理程序
depends on it okay
取决于它好吗
we also have feedback here at run time
我们在运行时也有反馈
as to the URL of these of this mapping
关于此映射的URL
so I can mouse over this it says yeah if
所以我可以将鼠标悬停在上面，说是的
I were to go to localhost 8080 for size
我要去本地主机8080
reservations right now I would be able
现在可以预定
to see this endpoint and surely as can
可以肯定地看到这个端点
be I do sit in port when I click on an
是的，当我单击
in point I can see all the data there
我可以看到那里的所有数据
I've written more than a few records
我写了几笔唱片
over the last several days and to the
在过去的几天里，
same point so we know that that's
同一点，所以我们知道那是
working okay
工作正常
now i-i've seen these endpoints I've
现在我已经看到了这些端点
seen the navigation here I've got a
在这里看到了导航
couple of different endpoints don't I
几个不同的端点不是吗
i've got i've got the the endpoint
我有终点
that's defined here by this handler the
该处理程序在此处定义的
logic for this is in the handler if I
如果我这样做的逻辑是在处理程序中
click on that I can see that you know
点击，我可以看到你知道
that that endpoint is providing business
该端点正在提供业务
logic for me if I make it public you
如果我公开给你，对我来说就是逻辑
know we can also see that it says that
知道我们也可以看到它说
this is an endpoint that you know it
这是您知道的端点
actually shows me the mapping annotation
实际上给我看了映射注解
if I make it public as well so that's
如果我也将其公开，那就是
very convenient and I get the you know I
非常方便，我得到你知道的我
get the ability to see what this
有能力看到这个
endpoint is what URI this endpoint lives
端点是此端点存在的URI
at at what point and what you or I this
在什么时候以及什么时候您或我
endpoint is mounted basically it's
端点安装基本上是
mounted at four sash reservations for
安装在四个窗扇上
sash ID and response stage should be get
窗框ID和响应阶段
and that's nice because my handler very
那很好，因为我的经理非常
well might live in a separate code page
可能会住在单独的代码页中
altogether for example I could alt
举例来说，我完全可以
command T and just move this to a new
命令T并将其移动到新
type file write a new file and when I do
键入文件，写一个新文件，当我这样做
that you know everything is you know
你知道一切都知道
semantically structurally it's all the
从语义上讲，这就是
same exactly but my my request mapping
完全一样，但是我的请求映射
routing logic is nowhere to be found
找不到路由逻辑
it's in a separate code page all
它在单独的代码页中
together so it's nice I don't have to
在一起，所以很好，我不必
switch back and forth between the two
在两者之间来回切换
different code pages to see that this is
不同的代码页，看到这是
mounted at for test reservations for
安装在进行测试预订
touch ID I have the ability to navigate
触摸ID，我可以导航
very easily I can say command six and if
我可以很容易地说出命令六，如果
I say for example add command or at the
我说例如add命令或
at symbol at component it shows me
在组件上的符号处显示给我
everything at its annotate with add
一切都用添加来注释
component and everything in this meta
组件以及此meta中的所有内容
transitively with that component so for
与该组件的传递
example reservation handler reservation
预订处理程序预订示例
rest controller which is itself
rest controller 本身
annotated with address controller which
带有地址控制器的注释
is itself annotate with that controller
本身用那个控制器注释
which is itself annotate with that
这本身就是注释
component reservation service
零件预定服务
application is annotated with Springwood
应用程序用Springwood注释
application which is annotated spring
注释弹簧的应用程序
boot configuration which is annotated
带有注释的启动配置
with configuration which is annotated
带有注释的配置
component so you can see this like
组件，这样您就可以看到
really interesting sort of navigability
真正有趣的可导航性
here and I can click on this and it'll
在这里，我可以单击它，它将
take me to the code page for that for
带我到代码页
that end point if I do command 6 again
如果我再次执行命令6
and do forward slash it shows me all the
并向前斜线显示所有
URLs that are available in this
在此可用的URL
application right and it's me click on
申请权，是我点击
them and I can see them in action so I
他们，我可以看到他们的行动，所以我
have this really nice navigated
有这个非常好的导航
navigability in the application itself
应用程序本身的可导航性
and that's all based on this sort of
而这一切都是基于这种
runtime awareness that the spring tool
spring tool的运行时意识
suite 4 has for me ok now I like my
套房4对我来说好吧，现在我喜欢我的
application it's certainly a simple
应用程序肯定很简单
application that said I wanna be able to
说我想要的应用程序
run this in production and I'm running
在生产中运行它，我正在运行
at my local machine you see how easy it
在我的本地计算机上，您会发现它多么容易
is to start and stop and and do all
是开始和停止，然后做所有
these kinds of things but what I want to
这些事情，但我想
do is I'm gonna actually deploy this to
我要做的是将其实际部署到
Cloud Foundry now climb time use a
Cloud Foundry现在可以使用
platform is a service it's open source
平台是开源的服务
I'm gonna connect two pivotal web
我要连接两个关键网络
services which is a multi-tenant hosted
多租户托管的服务
instance of cloud from a running on
运行中的云实例
Amazon in the East region by default and
默认情况下，东部地区的亚马逊和
I'm gonna deploy this application to it
我要将此应用程序部署到它
and I'm gonna just be able to see what
我将能够看到什么
it's doing from there so I've already
它是从那里做的，所以我已经
got a Cloud Foundry target all you have
有一个Cloud Foundry目标
to do is you click on plus sign click on
要做的就是单击加号单击
Cloud Foundry target fill out the form
Cloud Foundry目标填写表格
you know email password you know the
您知道电子邮件密码
things that you care about for your
您关心的事情
platform for your card for instance once
例如您的卡平台
you've signed up for an account and I
您已经注册了一个帐户，而我
wanted to play the application now I you
我想现在就播放应用程序
know I remember what's to remember that
知道我还记得那件事
remember the defaults command shift are
记住默认的命令移位是
will show me the proper resources and
会告诉我适当的资源，
open up my property file
打开我的财产文件
I have no configuration here I didn't
我在这里没有配置
say spring that Mongo Mongo dot anything
说春天，蒙哥蒙哥点点什么
really right I haven't specified Mongo
是的，我还没有指定Mongo
anything so I haven't specified logging
任何东西，所以我还没有指定日志记录
I can specify all sorts of things I
我可以指定各种各样的东西
could specify a server dot port right
可以指定服务器点端口权限
server that port you know server that
您知道该端口的服务器
port equals a t10 for example
例如，端口等于t10
if I hit save that'll restart the
如果我点击保存，将重新启动
application and the application is now
应用程序，现在该应用程序
spun up on port 80 10 right so I can do
在端口80 10上旋转，这样我可以
all sorts of things with this property
带有此属性的各种事物
file you can see that that spring tool
文件，您可以看到该spring tool
suite for is really smart it shows me
套件真的很聪明，它告诉我
different configuration values that I
我的不同配置值
can use to to change they built an
可以用来改变他们建立了
application that said I haven't
说我还没有的申请
specified a MongoDB URL and I don't want
指定了MongoDB URL，但我不想
to in my local machine in development
在我本地开发的机器上
it's working just fine I don't need to
它工作正常，我不需要
specify URL but when I connect this to
指定URL，但是当我将其连接到
Cloud Foundry that the information as to
关于Cloud Foundry的信息
how I can how it should connect to a
我如何才能将其连接到
MongoDB that'll be buried in the
将被埋在MongoDB中
environment the environment variables in
环境中的环境变量
the running process in the platform and
平台中的运行过程
those environment variables get turned
这些环境变量被打开
into properties that are visible to my
变成我可见的属性
Springwood application when they're
当他们使用Springwood应用程序时
running in Cloud Foundry so what I need
在Cloud Foundry中运行，所以我需要
to do is I need to tell spring hey this
要做的是我要告诉春天嘿
is some configuration that is only going
是一些只会用的配置
to be available when you're running in
在您运行时可用
card funding otherwise just use the
卡注资，否则只需使用
default configuration and that
默认配置
configuration is then we I'm going to
配置，那么我们要去
separate it out I'm going to tease it
分开我要去逗它
away from the rest of the code by using
通过使用远离其他代码
a profile a profile is just a tag it's a
个人资料只是个人资料的标签
label and I can do this for objects and
标签，我可以对对象执行此操作
for configuration I could for example go
对于配置，我可以例如去
here and say this is a beam an object
在这里说这是一个光束
that lives under the you know demo
在您知道的演示下
profile right so I say add profile and
个人资料正确，所以我说添加个人资料，
springwells automatically make this beam
弹跳井自动使该光束
not exist so if I restart the
不存在，所以如果我重新启动
application right now you can see that
现在，您可以看到
it restarted right now it just restart
现在重新启动，只是重新启动
automatically because I've got the dev
自动，因为我有开发人员
tools no logging on the console right
工具没有在控制台上登录的权利
nothing there that's because I haven't
那里什么都没有，因为我没有
explicitly activated this profile and
明确激活此个人资料并
because I did not do that this beam is
因为我没有做到这一点
effectively does not exist why would you
实际上不存在，为什么你会
want such a thing well again imagine
想要这样的事情再想像
without imagine you're doing the kind of
没想到你正在做那种
thing I'm doing I'm gonna take a
我正在做的事我会采取
development environment artifact and
开发环境工件和
promote it to a production environment I
推广到生产环境我
don't want my localhost username and
不想我的本地主机名和
password you know being used to try and
您知道用来尝试输入的密码
talk to the production database and
与生产数据库交谈，
similarly I don't want my production
同样，我不要我的作品
database credentials buried in the code
代码中埋藏的数据库凭据
so I might want to have a separate set
所以我可能想单独订一套
of configuration that draws its
绘制其配置的
configuration from an external source
来自外部来源的配置
okay so I can do that for objects and I
好吧，我可以为对象做这些，我
can't also do that for this config file
也无法为此配置文件执行此操作
that I showed you the properties file
我给你看了属性文件
called application up properties so I'm
叫应用程序属性，所以我
going to do that I'm gonna go to source
要做那我要去来源
main resources
主要资源
I'll create a new file called
我将创建一个名为
application - cloud dot properties and
应用程序-云点属性和
I'm gonna give it a very specific
我要给它一个非常具体的
configuration here I'm going to say cat
这里的配置我要说的是猫
desktop application clouds up properties
桌面应用程序使属性模糊
I'm going to copy that into the
我将其复制到
clipboard and paste so a spring data
剪贴板并粘贴弹簧数据
among going to be your I equals and this
其中将成为你我等于
property that references a MongoDB
引用MongoDB的属性
instance that I've given a logical name
我给了逻辑名的实例
called my MongoDB that's running in the
叫我的MongoDB在
platform that's only gonna be accessible
只能访问的平台
that property file will only be active
该属性文件将仅处于活动状态
when the profile for cloud is active and
当云配置文件处于活动状态时，
in order for that to be active we need
为了使它活跃起来，我们需要
to create a Cloud Foundry manifest so
创建一个Cloud Foundry清单
I'm gonna do that here there we go new
我要在这里做
manifest dot yellow paste all that in
明显的点黄色粘贴所有
alright so I've got an environment
好吧，我有一个环境
variable that's gonna tell spring it's
会告诉spring的变量
gonna tell Cloud Foundry just let me go
告诉Cloud Foundry就让我走
ahead and create the MongoDB instance
并创建MongoDB实例
I'm just gonna say go ahead and act it
我只是说继续吧
I'm gonna use an environment variable
我要使用环境变量
here spring profiles active spring boot
这里的弹簧型材主动式 spring boot
automatically normalizes this so spring
自动将其标准化，以便春季
boot will turn it into a lowercase
开机会将它变成小写
spring dot profiles dot active all
弹簧点轮廓点活动所有
lowercase and the value will be equal to
小写，该值将等于
cloud so what I'm telling cloud fund is
云，所以我要说的是云基金
I'm saying go ahead and deploy my
我是说继续部署我的
application as go spring go just go
随心所欲的申请
spring tell it to set up these
春天告诉它设置这些
environment variables for the running
运行的环境变量
application so the application behaves a
应用程序的行为
little differently so that the profile
稍有不同，因此配置文件
called cloud is active and thus so that
所谓的云是活跃的，因此
it'll draw this property file in
它将在
addition to the existing application of
除了现有的应用
properties and draw this into the
属性并将其绘制到
environment and use that to inform where
环境并以此来告知
to find the the MongoDB instance and
查找MongoDB实例，并
then finally I've told it to bind the
然后最后我告诉它绑定
already provisioned among would you be
已经准备好了吗
instance to make that instance visible
实例以使该实例可见
to my running application so that I can
到正在运行的应用程序，以便我可以
connect to it it'll put the connection
连接到它会把连接
credentials all that kind of stuff in
凭据所有此类内容
the environment and I'm gonna use that
环境，我要用它
to to connect to it that's what that
连接到那就是那个
property is telling MongoDB to do okay
属性告诉MongoDB可以做
so that's there now this is you know I'm
所以现在在那里，这就是你知道我在
using the spring tool suite for there's
使用spring工具套件
some really nice configuration support
一些非常好的配置支持
here I can customize everything I want
在这里我可以自定义我想要的一切
about the application using this ayat'
关于使用此ayat的应用程序'
this tooling but you know i already have
这个工具，但是你知道我已经有了
one so it's fine uh one thing that's
一件事很好，一件事是
kind eyes is if i didn't know the name
仁慈的眼睛是如果我不知道名字
of the service and with that in place I
的服务，到位的我
can have hit control space and it'll
可以拥有控制空间，它将
show me all the different connectable
告诉我所有不同的可连接性
backing services including Maya MongoDB
支持服务，包括Maya MongoDB
for example okay with that in place
例如，就可以了
I've got Cloud Foundry here I can take
我在这里有Cloud Foundry
my application just drag it on the cart
我的应用程序将其拖到购物车上
render right and it's gonna said you
渲染正确，它会说你
want to use this manifest I'll say
想用这个清单我会说
absolutely
绝对
I want to enable the JMX SSH tunnel that
我要启用的JMX SSH隧道
could be useful for debugging later and
可能对以后的调试很有用，并且
I hit go
我去了
you
您
so there we are there's the application
所以这里有应用程序
it started up you can see the output as
它启动了，您可以看到输出为
it's showing up in the server itself in
它显示在服务器本身中
Cloud Foundry right here's the
Cloud Foundry就在这里
application if I go back to my
如果我回到我的应用程序
application code here for example I can
例如，这里我可以使用应用程序代码
see not only the localhost version of
不仅看到的本地版本
the endpoint but also now the URL for
端点，现在还有URL
the application running a Cloud Foundry
运行Cloud Foundry的应用程序
HTTP Co spring cff star IO etc and it
HTTP Co spring cff star IO等
shows me the data there isn't that cool
告诉我数据没有那么酷
I I get now instant feedback from both
II现在从双方获得即时反馈
the local and my cloud environment I can
我可以在本地和我的云环境中
do things like debugging and all sorts
做诸如调试之类的事情
of things I can administer a lot of
我可以管理很多事情
different running applications from the
来自不同的正在运行的应用程序
the boot dashboard you get all this for
启动仪表板，您可以获得所有这些
free right you get this all just this
自由权，你就得到这一切
nice in ID experience i can do i can
我能做的ID体验很好
write software test it debugging connect
编写软件测试调试连接
to the cloud platform get it up and
安装到云平台
running and see how it's looking and so
跑步，看看它的样子等等
on
上
swing tool suite for you know it's it's
摆动工具套件，您知道的是
a very compelling because it gives me a
非常引人注目，因为它给了我一个
one-stop shop where i can create a new
一站式商店，我可以在其中创建新商品
project i can write code using it using
我可以使用它编写代码的项目
using a world-class Java editor and a
使用世界一流的Java编辑器和
debugger and so on I get smart insight
调试器等，我获得了明智的见解
when in auto-completion for things like
自动完成时，例如
Java and for things like my property
Java和诸如我的财产之类的东西
files and my Cod funding manifests I get
文件和我的鳕鱼资金清单证明我得到了
insight about the running application
关于正在运行的应用程序的见解
which is the only real accurate
这是唯一真正准确的
information right there's no false
信息正确，没有错误
positives here you're getting feedback
积极在这里，您正在获得反馈
about the running application and
关于正在运行的应用程序以及
nothing less it doesn't show you it
没什么不告诉你的
doesn't try and second-guess the the
不会尝试并再次猜测
metamodel that spring is already built
春天已经建立的元模型
up for it's running object raft
准备好运行对象筏
it just looks at that directly based on
它只是直接基于
the running help application itself we
正在运行的帮助应用程序本身
can see that navigate navigability is
可以看到导航可导航性是
key right so if i do forward slash it
正确的关键，所以如果我向前斜杠
shows me now not just my localhost
显示给我的不仅仅是我的本地主机
endpoints but also my cloud foundry
端点，还有我的云代工厂
endpoints right they're ones that are
正确的端点是
deployed in cloud for me as well so I
我也将其部署在云中
have all that just by doing forward
通过前进就拥有所有这些
slash forward slash at you know at is
斜线正斜杠，你知道是
really your key here and I'll show you
真的是你的钥匙，我会告诉你
all the sort of interesting things that
各种各样有趣的事情
you could do and the application so
你可以做的和应用程序这样
again just lots of really interesting
再次只是很多非常有趣
things that are discoverable I would say
我会说的发现的东西
I think that's like one of the really
我认为那是真正的
compelling features here is that you
引人注目的功能是您
know anybody can build a car
知道任何人都可以制造汽车
and Java IDE at this point there's a
和Java IDE，这时
number of different tools out there that
各种不同的工具
are for that but when it comes to
是为此而设计的
building Enterprise great applications
建立企业出色的应用程序
that are that are connected to the to
那些连接到
production they're oriented from
他们面向的生产
production that are large enough that it
足够大的产品
becomes sort of unwieldy having the
变得有点笨拙
ability to navigate quickly from one
从一个快速导航的能力
thing to another to see what it depends
事情到另一个，看看它取决于什么
on the other what how things interact
另一方面，事物如何相互作用
that I think is a different shooter so
我认为是一个不同的射手，所以
my friends we've we've built a very
我的朋友们，我们已经建立了一个非常
simple application we've built an
我们已经构建了一个简单的应用程序
application that is has a reactive web
具有反应式Web的应用程序
endpoint and some reactive data access
端点和一些反应式数据访问
we used the dev tools to support live
我们使用了开发工具来支持实时
reloading and to support you know
重新加载并支持您知道
insight into the application we've also
洞察应用程序，我们也
used Lum sorry the actuator actuator is
二手Lum对不起，执行器
a set of endpoints that are added to the
一组添加到
application automatically for us and
自动为我们申请
that actuator information is visible in
在以下位置可见执行器信息
cloud foundry and then it feeds back
云铸造厂，然后反馈
into the insight that you see here
您在这里看到的见解
that's why these URLs reflect what's
这就是为什么这些URL反映了什么
happening in cuffin is because that
发生在袖扣中是因为
actuator inside cloud funding itself if
如果资金本身，云内部的执行器
you go to cloud vendors apps manager
你去云供应商的应用程序经理
it'll also show you information being
它还会向您显示信息
fed off of being you know sort of
受够了你知道
drained off of the actuator endpoint in
从执行器端点排出
the application itself it'll surface
应用程序本身就会浮出水面
that in a single pane of glass that
在一块玻璃中
ever-important a single pane of glass or
非常重要的是一块玻璃或
dashboard experience in the cloud
云中的仪表板体验
pending apps manager so you get a lot of
待定的应用程序经理，因此您可以获得很多
value out of that and of course we're
重视其中，我们当然
building a reactive web application we
构建一个反应式Web应用程序，我们
have data access what we didn't write is
可以访问数据我们没有写的是
almost as important as where we is what
几乎和我们在哪里一样重要
we got right what we didn't write is any
我们说对了，我们没有写的是
code or nor do we have to care about
代码还是我们也不必关心
anything related to deploying or
与部署或
managing our server let alone a reactive
管理我们的服务器，更不用说反应式
Neddie based server
基于Neddie的服务器
this is Neddie starting a port in India
这是Neddie在印度开始的港口
- it's blazing fast and asynchronous and
-快速而异步
efficient we didn't worry about
高效，我们不用担心
connecting to MongoDB we worry about
连接到我们担心的MongoDB
doing anything really we just wrote the
做任何事情，实际上我们只是写了
code there that speaks to our business
与我们业务相关的代码
requirement and we wrote code that is
需求，我们写的代码是
testable so of course I haven't really
可测试的，所以我当然不是
touched on testing in this in this video
触及了这个视频中的测试
but all these all this code is written
但是所有这些代码都被编写了
using constructor injection which means
使用构造函数注入意味着
I can provide the collaborating objects
我可以提供合作对象
using a mock if I want to I can test
如果愿意，可以使用模拟游戏
just the initializer for example or just
例如初始化器或仅
the reservation rest controller in
预订 rest controller
isolation so you get all that by writing
隔离，因此您可以通过编写来获得所有这些
clean object-oriented code it is very
干净的面向对象代码非常
easy to to extract things - to refactor
容易提取东西-重构
things in the ID I used Oh
我用的ID里的东西哦
command T and I'll command s quite a bit
命令T，我要命令s
to refactorings and extractions and that
重构和提取，以及
kind of thing and the results as I can
我可以做的事情和结果
you know I can prototype very quickly
你知道我可以很快原型
and I can make mistakes and then if I
我会犯错，然后如果我
get to a point where I feel like things
达到我感觉像东西的地步
are stable I can extract them out into
是稳定的，我可以将它们提取到
separate types and you know the results
单独的类型，您知道结果
I think speaks for itself thanks very
我认为不言而喻非常感谢
much for watching and we'll see you next
收看很多，我们下次见
time
时间